sometimes you're in a relationship and you're there and everything is what it is and then you
reach a point where you're like i know this is a good person but i'm just really not interested
in being with them no more have you ever seen the movie blue valentine with ryan gosling and
michelle williams first of all when i saw the movie me and my homegirl emily we literally had
to sit in the theater for like 30 minutes after just like in a stupor because we were just like
wow maybe this love thing really doesn't matter really but honestly like that movie was a great
example of even though this man loved this woman to the brim to the hilt even though he saw her
through her darkest time she just reached a point where he just couldn't fulfill her to where she
had gotten to and then she felt like she was such a bad person for not wanting to be with him anymore
you gotta be honest with yourself and the risk in those situations comes in well will something
better come along if i exit this situation that i wanted so badly and that i've put so much time
into will something better come along and you gotta believe that yes it will
you yeah
yeah
and